Hello friends, welcome back to my channel.
Our car had an accident and today
we will tell you how you can
claim the insurance taken from Policy Bazaar.
First I will show you the damage and
then I will tell you the complete process and will also take
you to the service
center where we will
follow the entire procedure and show you each and every thing
step by step. Friends, this is
our car which was
damaged due to the accident. You see, its
left side headlight was broken and
its front bumper was also completely damaged.
Now you can see that
it is completely damaged. There was also some damage from the rear.
Look, the joint was opened.
Today we will go to the service center and
show you the complete procedure of the claim
and what things can be claimed and what
things cannot be claimed. Which buttons have to be taken
care of. All these things are
understood in this video. So
friends, let's move ahead and see the process of the claim.
Friends, this is it.  The cashless garage to which
Policy Bazaar sent me, when my
car met with an accident, I
immediately called the
insurance helpline of PolicyBhajo.com. They
gave me the addresses of all the cashless garages in my area, from which
I selected a cashless garage and then
I told the company that
I would get my car insured under cashless insurance. Policy
Bazaar immediately gave me the number of that cashless garage
and also
gave my number to the cashless garage and within 5 minutes
I got a call from this cashless garage and
asked when will you come now, I told him
that brother I will come tomorrow, he
showed me all the documents that were required like
driving license, RC of the car, pollution and
copy of insurance, I had to take all these documents,
I did not have to take any other paper, he made the entire
claim and only got my signature,
he also took the photo of all the documents himself and the formalities of the claim were completed,
after that
he did this  After completing all the formalities, I
sent it to the insurance company which was insured for me. The
next day was Sunday, so the insurance
company was divided and the next day i.e. Monday, there was
this cashless garage band, so my claim
procedure started from Tuesday, then the
company was conducting a survey, in which
my car was surveyed and whatever things were
passable, he told me everything and
then within the next five days, the approval was given from there,
you can see my
car was opened like this and all these damages
which I have already shown you, like the
damage on the back side, the surveyor did not pass them,
he said that brother, your car has been hit from the front, which
means it was already damaged
because friends, the insurance company gives claim only for the
accident that happened in the last seven days, it does
not give old claims,
hence these claims were not made, only the front
bumper and the headlight were
included in the claim and the insurance company gave
me a total claim for all those things.  The
insurance company's claim was
around 8500 rupees, so they
approved it, and then the car's work began.
Friends, finally, our insurance claim in Rajan's state has been
completely completed, and today we are getting the car.
We got this car after 10 days
because our insurance company had
delayed releasing the payment.
Look, the company has replaced our bumper
and also replaced the headlights. I had requested the owner of the cashless car to
paint the damaged areas.
They painted the rear side, so the
damage is no longer visible.
They also repaired the gap at the back.
They did
not charge me any extra for this. The
cashless car owners work very well,
because they want you to
promote them if you work well. They will tell people what kind of
cashless car they are, which is working well out of
greed.  Our vehicle is
managed very well, so friends, the
insurance claim experience from Policy Bazaar has
been quite good, you
can get insurance from Policy Bazaar, there is
no problem.